<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="doc_agreement_content">USER AGREEMENT\n\nThis User Agreement (the \"Agreement\") governs the relationship between the user of the PROFI-A mobile application (the \"User\") and the application right holder (the \"Operator\") in connection with the use of the PROFI-A application (the \"Application\").\n\n1. GENERAL PROVISIONS\n1.1. Installing the Application, registering in it and starting to use it constitute the User\'s unconditional acceptance of the terms of this Agreement in accordance with Art. 437, 438 of the Civil Code of the Russian Federation (acceptance of the offer).\n1.2. If the User does not agree with the terms of the Agreement, use of the Application is not permitted.\n\n2. SUBJECT OF THE AGREEMENT\n2.1. The Operator grants the User the right to use the Application under a simple (non-exclusive) licence in accordance with its functional purpose: preparation of estimates for construction and repair work, management of projects and premises, preparation of reports and acts.\n2.2. Use of the Application is carried out in accordance with the rules set out in the Agreement, the Privacy Policy and the personal data processing documentation.\n\n3. RIGHTS AND OBLIGATIONS OF THE USER\n3.1. The User agrees to use the Application only for lawful purposes, without violating the legislation of the Russian Federation and the rights of third parties.\n3.2. The User may not copy, decompile, modify or distribute the Application code and materials without the Operator\'s written consent.\n3.3. The User is responsible for the accuracy of the data entered and the security of login credentials.\n\n4. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY\n4.1. The Application is provided \"as is\". The Operator does not guarantee uninterrupted operation and is not liable for indirect damages, lost profits or harm arising from the use or inability to use the Application, unless otherwise provided by the legislation of the Russian Federation.\n4.2. Estimates and calculations generated in the Application are indicative; the User is solely responsible for commercial decisions.\n\n5. CHANGES TO THE TERMS\n5.1. The Operator may change the terms of the Agreement. The new version takes effect upon publication in the Application or on the Operator\'s website, unless otherwise stated. Continued use of the Application after the changes take effect constitutes acceptance of the new version.\n\n6. APPLICABLE LAW\n6.1. The legislation of the Russian Federation applies to this Agreement and the relationship between the User and the Operator. All disputes shall be resolved in accordance with the applicable legislation of the Russian Federation.\n\n7. OPERATOR DETAILS\nFor questions related to the Agreement, contact the Operator using the details specified in the \"About\" section and in the Privacy Policy.\n\nDate of publication: 2026.</string>

    <string name="doc_personal_data_content">PERSONAL DATA PROCESSING INFORMATION\n\nThis document has been prepared in accordance with Federal Law No. 152-FZ of 27 July 2006 \"On Personal Data\" (152-FZ) of the Russian Federation and defines the Operator\'s policy regarding the processing of personal data of users of the PROFI-A mobile application (the \"Application\").\n\n1. OPERATOR\nThe personal data operator is the right holder of the PROFI-A Application (the \"Operator\"). Contact details are specified in the \"About\" section and in the Privacy Policy.\n\n2. PURPOSES OF PROCESSING\nProcessing is carried out for: providing access to the Application and performing contractual relations; identifying the User during registration and login; communicating with the User (support, notifications); and complying with the legislation of the Russian Federation.\n\n3. LEGAL BASIS\nProcessing is based on: the data subject\'s consent (Art. 6 of 152-FZ); necessity for the performance of a contract; and compliance with applicable law.\n\n4. CATEGORIES OF DATA\nDepending on use, the following may be processed: name, email, phone, account data, organisation details (for sole traders/LLCs), project and estimate data, and technical/device data to the extent necessary for the Application.\n\n5. RETENTION AND DELETION\nPersonal data are stored for the duration of the contractual relationship and thereafter as required by the legislation of the Russian Federation. After the expiry of the retention period, data are deleted or anonymised.\n\n6. DATA SUBJECT RIGHTS\nUnder Art. 14 of 152-FZ, the User has the right to: obtain information on the processing of their personal data; request rectification, blocking or erasure where data are inaccurate or processed unlawfully; and withdraw consent (the Operator may continue processing where permitted by law). To exercise these rights, contact the Operator using the details in the Application.\n\n7. SECURITY MEASURES\nThe Operator implements organisational and technical measures to protect personal data in accordance with 152-FZ and applicable regulations.\n\n8. DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES\nDisclosure to third parties is carried out only where required by law or with the data subject\'s consent. Where cloud or server providers are used, the Operator ensures that agreements comply with 152-FZ.\n\n9. CHANGES\nThe Operator may update this document. The current version is published in the Application. Continued use after publication may be treated as acceptance where permitted by law.\n\nDate of publication: 2026.</string>

    <string name="doc_privacy_policy_content">PRIVACY POLICY\n\nThis Privacy Policy (the \"Policy\") describes how we collect, use, store and protect information about users of the PROFI-A mobile application (the \"Application\") in accordance with the legislation of the Russian Federation, including Federal Law No. 152-FZ \"On Personal Data\" and Federal Law No. 149-FZ \"On Information, Information Technologies and the Protection of Information\".\n\n1. OPERATOR\nThe operator determining the purposes and means of processing is the right holder of the PROFI-A Application. Contact details are available in the \"About\" section.\n\n2. INFORMATION WE COLLECT\n— Data provided during registration and in the profile: name, email, phone, organisation details.\n— Data created when using the Application: projects, rooms, estimates, acts, settings.\n— Technical data: device identifiers, session and error data to the extent necessary for operation and security.\n\n3. HOW WE USE INFORMATION\nInformation is used to: provide and improve the Application; authenticate and protect the account; communicate with the user; and comply with the law.\n\n4. STORAGE AND SECURITY\nData are stored on the user\'s device and, when using an account, on the Operator\'s servers or those of authorised parties. Organisational and technical measures are applied in accordance with 152-FZ. Retention periods correspond to the purposes of processing and applicable law.\n\n5. DISCLOSURE\nPersonal data are disclosed to third parties only where required by law or with the user\'s consent. Subcontractors are bound by personal data protection requirements.\n\n6. USER RIGHTS\nThe user has the right to access, rectify, block and erase their personal data, and to withdraw consent (see \"Personal data processing\" document). Contact the Operator using the details in the Application.\n\n7. CHANGES TO THE POLICY\nThe Operator may update the Policy. The new version takes effect upon publication in the Application. We recommend reviewing the current version periodically.\n\n8. CONTACTS\nFor questions regarding the Privacy Policy and personal data, contact the Operator via the \"Support\" section or the details in \"About\".\n\nDate of publication: 2026.</string>
</resources>
